Seriously, what's wrong with me?
〈（薫）私　ホントに
どうしちゃったんだろう？〉
〈突然　こんな気持ちに
なるなんてさ〉
Why do I suddenly feel this way?
《（純一）僕　薫に告白されるのかと
思っちゃったよ》
I thought you were gonna confess to me, Kaoru.
〈あいつとは
中学からの悪友でしょ！〉
Isn't he just a buddy I've had since middle school?!
No more, no less...
〈それ以上でも
それ以下でもなかったのに…〉
〈変わったのは　あいつじゃない
私の方だ〉
But he's not the one who's changed.
I am.
〈でも何で？　何でなの？〉
But why?  How come?
It's true that I'm not satisfied with our current relationship...
〈確かに
私には足りなかったけどさ〉
If you described it as a color, it'd be a pale pink.
〈色でいうなら　淡いピンク色が〉
〈でも急すぎるよ
分かんない　自分でも…〉
But it's all too sudden!
I don't even know what I want.
〈あ～あ　カッコ悪い〉
Ah, I'm so uncool.
〈同じとこばっか
くるくる回ってさ〉
I'm just going around in circles...
Geez, what's wrong with me?!
もう　何やってんのよ私！
Could it be that...
まさか　私…　恋してる！？
I'm in love?!
No.  No way.
いや　ないでしょ…　ないない
No, no.
フッ…
Nii-nii, what are you eating?
（美也）にぃに　何食べてんの？
うん？　食べていいよ
限定　塩大福味
You can have some.
It's the limited-edition stuffed rice cake flavor.
何か機嫌いいね
いいことあったの？
You seem happy.  Did something good happen?
Huh?  Not really.
えッ？　別に
ふ～ん
Oh?
Beaver
Romance of the
Three Kingdoms
うん？　何だよ美也
Beaver
Romance of the
Three Kingdoms
Beaver
Romance of the
Three Kingdoms
Beaver
Romance of the
Three Kingdoms
What's the matter, Miya?
Nothing.
別に～
These are actually good!
あッ　これ意外においしいね
ちょっと
まんま肉まんの味に似てるかも
They even taste a little like stuffed meat buns!
いや　似てないだろ
Uh, you've gotta be kidding.
I love you from my heart
・～
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
う～わッ　寒い
Brr, it's so cold!
ふざけてんじゃないわよ！
何すんだよ　棚町！
Don't screw with me!
What are you doing, Tanamachi?!
That's my line!
それは　こっちのセリフよ　あんた
人の気持ち考えたことあんの？
Did you even consider how she feels?!
いつまでもガキみたいなマネして
棚町には関係ないだろ
You're always acting like a kid!
This has nothing to do with you, Tanamachi.
直接はね　だけどあんな陰湿なこと
周りでやられるとイライラするのよ！
Not directly, no.
But it pisses me off when you do such malicious things to people around me!
Well, does it feel that good to hurt the feelings of others?!
ねえ　人を傷つけるって
そんなに快感？
Think hard on what you've done with that empty head of yours!
からっぽの頭で自分が
したことをよく考えてみなさい
黙って聞いてりゃ　お前…
何よ　やる気？
If you'd just shut up and listen...
What?  You wanna fight?
H-Hang on!
ちょっと待てよ
うっさいわね！　事情も知らずに
Stay out of this!
You don't know what's going on, so keep your mouth shut!
口　出すんじゃないわよ！
事情は知らないけど見過ごせない
I may not know what's going on, but I can't just ignore it!
一体どうしたっていうんだ？
What on Earth is the matter?
What's the matter, Tanamachi-san?
（詞）どうしたの？　棚町さん
別に…　何でもないわよ
ちょっと待って　棚町さん
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Wait, Tanamachi-san!
おい　どこ行くんだよ
まったく　何だってんだよ
Hey, where are you going?!
Geez, what was that about?
だよな～　あんなことで　いちいち
目くじら立てんなってえの
Seriously, getting all worked up over something like that.
Hey.
ねえ　どういうことなの？
What happened?
・（男子生徒）
棚町が突っかかってきたんだ
Tanamachi lunged at me out of the blue.
For no reason?
理由もなく？
（恵子）私のせいなの
薫　私のために…
It's my fault.
Kaoru... did it for me...
What?
えッ？
薫
Kaoru.
なあ　一体何があったんだよ
Hey.  What exactly happened?
Could you tell me?
話してくれないか？
あいつら　恵子の手紙を
回し読みして笑ってたのよ
Those guys passed Keiko's letter around and laughed at it.
Wait, so he's the one Tanaka-san likes...
えッ　じゃあ
田中さんの相手って…
私の予感が
見事に当たっちゃったってわけよ
Everything happened the way I feared it would.
Since the whole kissing incident,
I knew he was that kind of person.
最初のキス事件のときから
あんなヤツって思ってたんだけど
でも　恵子が好きだって言うから
応援しようと思ったのに…
But Keiko said she liked him,
so I thought I'd give her my support.
恵子　あんたに言われて
ゆうべ　一生懸命書いたのよ　手紙
Keiko followed your advice and did her best to write the letter last night.
何度も何度も「これでどうかな？」
って私に電話してきて
She kept calling me over the phone and asking me, "how's this?"
Tanamachi Kaoru Arc
Chapter 2
Hesitation
メチャクチャなこと言われても
やっぱり好きだからって
She said that she still likes him even
though he says horrible things to her.
心を込めて
そうだったんだ…
With all her heart.
I see.
I tried to stay calm at first.
最初は我慢しようと思ったけど
あいつらの笑い声を聞いてたら…
But when I heard them laughing...
Sorry, Kaoru.
ゴメン　薫
うん？
何で　あんたが謝んのよ
Why are you apologizing?
それ知ってたら　止めなかったよ
If I'd known that, I wouldn't have stopped you.
いいって　どっちにしろ
あれ以上　言うつもりもなかったし
It's fine.
Either way, I didn't intend to say anything more to him.
それに　あんだけやっておけば
ちゃ～んと考えるでしょ
What's more, after all that, he'll definitely think it over.
考える？　何を？
恵子のこと
Think?  About what?
About Keiko.
どうだろうな…
I wonder about that...
Keiko's problem was that the guy she
confessed to never gave her an answer.
恵子の相談って　告白したのに彼が
返事をしてくれないことだったし
これでバッチリ解決！　でしょ？
The problem's completely solved now, isn't it?
Keiko knows what kind of guy
he is now, and I feel so much better.
恵子も　あいつがどんなヤツか
分かったし　私もスッキリしたし
お前がスッキリして
どうするんだよ
And how does your feeling better help the situation?
そっか　それもそうね
Oh, yeah.  You have a point.
Geez.
たく
私　寒いのは嫌いなんだけど
この季節の空は好きなんだよね
I don't really like the cold, but I like how the sky looks during the winter.
へえ～
うまく言えないけど
Oh?
How do I put it...
澄みきってて
やけに高く見えるな～って
It's nice and clear, and you can see really far up.
うん
終わり
Yeah.
The end.
えッ？
空の感想　終わり
Huh?
"Thoughts on the sky".  The end.
終わりなんだ
うん
That's it?
Yeah.
In that case, you're the one at fault.
それは　あなたが悪いわね
そういうことなら
In these circumstances, anyone would get mad.
It didn't have to be Tanamachi-san.
棚町さんじゃなくても
怒るんじゃないかしら
なあ薫　ラブレターの件で
分かったんだけど
Hey, Kaoru.
I kinda learned this through the love letter incident,
田中さんって　おとなしそうに
見えるけど結構　積極的なんだな
but Tanaka-san's pretty assertive despite her timid look.
うん　最初　私も驚いた
Yeah.  I was pretty surprised myself at first.
ハハッ　やっぱりそうなんだ
So you thought so too.
まあ　今回は
あんなことになっちゃったけどね
Well, things turned out pretty bad this time.
うん
でも　次は
Yeah.
But next time, I'll definitely make everything work out!
私が　どうにかしてみせるわ
そっと見守ってあげようよ
You should just watch over her quietly.
I guess.
そうだね
薫
うん？
Kaoru.
ちょっと聞きたいんだけど
I'd like to ask you something.
Do you have someone you like?
お前は好きなヤツとかいるのか？
えッ　何でそんなこと聞くのよ
W-Why do you need to know that?!
いや　何となく
Eh, no particular reason.
何となくか…
なあ　どうなんだ？
No particular reason?
Well, do you?
Can't you just tell me?
教えてくれたっていいだろ
イヤ
Don't wanna.
何だよそれ　ケチ
Why not?  Stingy.
じゃあさ
あんたはいるの？　好きな子
Well then, do you have a girl you like?
えッ？　いないよ
I don't.
ふ～ん　そう…
I see.
あんたと私の関係って　何だろうね
I wonder what you'd call our relationship?
はあ？　突然どうしたんだよ
Huh?  What made you say that?
I've been thinking about it.
ここんとこ考えてたのよね
私達って
どんな関係なんだろうって
I wonder what you'd call our relationship?
Even in high school, nothing's really changed from how we were in middle school.
高校に入ってからも中学んときと
ほとんど変わってないじゃない？
つかず離れずでフワフワしてる
We maintain a certain distance, all lukewarm.
It's such a vague relationship.
すごく中途半端な感じ
淡いパステル色みたいな…
Just like... pale pastel colors.
Pale... pastel?
淡い…　パステル？
パッ　パステルピンク…
P-Pastel pink...
I don't think you've learned your lesson yet.
あんた　まだ懲りてないのね
あッ　いやいやいや
何がパステルだって？
N-No, no, no.  So what about pastels?
It's an example to illustrate our relationship.
あんたと私の関係を
例えたんじゃない
あんたは何だと思う？
それなら悪友ってとこじゃ？
What would you call it?
Something like... buddies?
I guess that's about where we are.
まあ　そんな程度よね…
分かってた
I already knew that.
それで？
うん　だからさ
So?
Yeah, that's why...
そろそろ少しくらい変化が
あってもいいかなって思って
I was thinking it's about time to change it just a little.
Change, huh?
変化ね…
知り合ったのは中学だったけど
We met each other in middle school,
それから私達も
それなりに成長したわけだし
but we've matured quite a bit since then.
まあ　確かにそうだけど
Well, that's true.
でも　その変化ってのは
今の僕達には必要ないだろ？
But there's no need for a change in our relationship now, right?
そんなことない！
絶対絶対　必要なんだから！
T-That's not true!
It's definitely, definitely, needed!
どうして急にムキになるんだ？
What are you so worked up for?
I-I'm not worked up at all!
ムキになんてなってない！
はあ…　分かったよ
Okay.
お前が
何を考えてるのか分かんないけど
I don't really know what you're thinking,
but I'll play along with making a change if you want.
とりあえず
変化とやらに　つきあってやるよ
Well, what should we do?
どうすればいいんだ？
ああ…　それは全然考えてなかった
I didn't think about that at all.
そんなことだろうと思ったよ
I thought so.
じゃあ聞くけど　あんたには
こうしたいとかないの？
Well, lemme ask you.
Isn't there anything you want to do?
う～ん…　これといって
Not really.
Then give me some time.
じゃあ　ちょっと時間ちょうだい
考えるから
I'll think about it.
What do you mean, you'll think about it?
何だよ　考えるって…
まあ　いいけど
Well, okay.
（はるか）う～ん…
Haruka, it's about time you narrowed down your options.
（響）はるか　いい加減に
絞り込まなきゃダメよ
迷っちゃうな～　結構強くて
たくましい子もいいけど→
I'm lost.
A strong, sturdy one isn't bad,
私に甘えてくれる　小さくて
かわいい子も捨てがたいし…→
but I also really want a small, cute one that wants my affection.
Chemistry II
でも　やっぱりシッポは長い方が…
Though, maybe one with a long tail would be...
Chemistry II
（響）はるか　何の話してるの？
Haruka, what are you talking about?
進路でしょ　進路
We're talking about career plans, career plans.
何だ　それなら
私は文系の大学を受験予定
Oh?  Well then, I'm planning to test into a liberal arts university.
Yes, and we were talking about how you need to narrow down the course of study you'll follow.
（響）だから　その文系の
何学科を受けるのかを→
そろそろ
絞り込まないとって話でしょ
（はるか）ああ　そっか
Oh, I see.
よっし　決まり！
All right, I've decided!
うわッ　ちょっと待て
何も決まってないだろ！
Whoa, wait a minute!
You haven't decided anything at all!
お前…　何するつもりだ？
What are you gonna do?
い・い・こ・と
Something nice.
い・い・こ・と…　じゃないよ！
"Something nice"?
Quit fooling around!
うっさいわね　暴れんじゃないの！
Just shut up and stay still!
Kaoru!
薫！
抵抗したってムダよ
It's pointless to resist!
いや　だから！
おい　ウソだろ？
No, I mean...
Hey, you've gotta be kidding...
W-Wai- Kaoru...
えッ　ちょ…　薫　うおッ！
バカバカ！　あんたが暴れるから
ホントにしちゃったじゃない！
Y-You idiot!
Now we actually kissed because you couldn't stay still!
えッ？
冗談のつもりだったのに…
This was supposed to be just a joke...
ええ～ッ！
いや　でも　それはだな…
But uh, this means...
初めてだったのよ
It was my first.
ゴメン…
S-Sorry.
That didn't count!
今のはナシってことで！
はッ？
ノーカウント！
いい？　じゃあね
No count!
Got it?  Bye.
あッ　待てよ！
僕だって初めてだったんだ
W-Wait!
That was my first too!
You're gonna run away after stealing a kiss from me?!
僕の唇　奪って
逃げるつもりなのか？
ベーッ！
ノーカウント？
No count?
（チャイム）
（梅原）おうッ　大将　今日はまた
すっげえお宝本を手に入れ…
Sup, boss.
I got my hands on another porn mag today...
Sorry, Umehara.
悪いな　梅原
今日はやることがあるんだ
I have plans for today.
What's with him?
どうなってんだ？
薫
Kaoru.
何？
さっきの仕返しだ　図書室に来い
W-What is it?
Revenge for earlier.
Come to the library room.
えッ？
いいから来いよ
Whatever, just come.
何よ…
What was that for?
へえ　こりゃ何かおもしれえことに
なりそうなんじゃねえの？
This seems like it'll get interesting.
まさか
来ないってことないだろうな
She'll come, won't she?
（梨穂子）だから　うちの部は
本当は「さどう」じゃなくて
So apparently...
Our Tea Club isn't actually pronounced Sadou , but Chadou .
「ちゃどう」なんだって
（香苗）へえ
Oh?  Our school is an Urasenke.
うちの学校　裏千家だったんだ
えッ　そうなの？
茶道部のあんたが知らないの？
Oh, really?
Wait, you're in the Tea Club and you don't know about it?
Nope.  Not at all.
うん　全然知らなかったよ
フフッ…
あッ　純一
Ah, Junichi!
You're as spacey as ever.
またそんなボケたことを
ねえ　たまに桜井の言いたいこと
I know, right?
Sometimes the things you say, Sakurai...
分かんないんだよね
ボケてんのかマジなのか
I can't tell if you're being serious or not.
I think she's mostly serious, which is why they end up dumb.
ほとんどマジだけど
それがボケてるってことだろ
That's mean.
ひどいよ～
でも　ホントだよ
It's true though.
桜井の思考回路
特別なんだもん
Your way of thinking is pretty special, Sakurai.
Oh, wait!
ああ　待ってよ～
じゃあね　純一
See you, Junichi!
あッ
（紗江）ここ　テストに出るかな？
I wonder if this will be on the test.
（逢）多分　出ると思う
ありがとう
I think it will.
Thanks.
Hey, wanna come over to my place for Christmas?
ねえ　クリスマスなんだけどさ
うちに来ない？
Huh?
（逢・紗江）えッ？
みんなで一緒に　ケーキ食べようよ
We can all have cake together!
楽しそう…　行きたいな
That sounds fun.  I'd like to go.
逢ちゃんは？
ゴメン
Ai-chan, what about you?
Sorry.  My family is getting together for a party.
うちは家族そろって
パーティーするから
I see.
そうなんだ
あッ　でも私のことは気にしないで
Ah, but don't worry about me.
２人はパーティーしたら？
The two of you can have a party.
A two-person party...
２人でパーティーか…
そうしよっか？
You want to?
うん
楽しみ楽しみ～　うん？
Sure.
This is gonna be great!
（紗江）あッ　あれ
美也ちゃんのお兄さんじゃ…
Miya-chan, isn't that your brother?
さっきのお返し　キッチリ
させてもらうぞ　男らしくな
I'm gonna get you back for earlier.
Like a man.
へえ～　男らしくね
Oh?  Like a man, huh?
ヘッ
うッ　何　その手つき？
What's with those hands?
The last time I tickled your sides, you almost died laughing.
前に薫の脇腹くすぐったら
笑い死にしそうになったろ
So prepare to meet the same fate!
だから　また同じ目に…
You'll regret this.
後悔するわよ
覚悟のうえだ
I'm ready for this.
ここは力ずくでも…
Even if I have to do this by force...
はあ～ッ！
はあ～ッ…
アハハハ…
やめてやめて　アハハハ…
Stop, stop!
No, I can't!
〈ダメだダメだ〉
This won't make me feel any better.
こんなんじゃ全然　納得できないし
仕返しにならない
It's not revenge at all.
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
何ブツブツ言ってんのよ
う～ん…
うん？
Mysteries of the
Human Body
That's it.
これだ　これだ！
That's it!
よし！　ヘソにキスをする！
All right!
I'm gonna kiss your belly button!
What?  Are you serious?!
はあッ？　本気？
本気だ
Dead serious!
そう　でも　もし私が
イヤって言ったらどうするの？
I see.
But what if I say no?
Are you gonna?
イヤって言うのか？
どうしよっかな～
I dunno...
そッ　それはナシで
I-I take that back...
That's not manly at all.
男らしくな～い
分かった
F-Fine.
だったら薫がイヤって言っても
無理やりする！
Even if you say no, I'll do it by force!
じゃあ…　いいよって言ったら？
Then... what if I say okay?
ええッ？
ねえ　どうするの？
Well, what would you do?
う～ん…　そしたら全力でする
In that case, I'll give it all I've got.
アハハハ…
アハハハ…　フハハハ…
W-What?!
何だよ！
さすがね～
I should've known!  You really are funny!
あんた　やっぱ面白いわ
Revenge for earlier, you said?
さっきの仕返しをするんだっけ？
分かった
You've got it.
見せてもらうわよ
あんたの男らしさを
Let's see your manliness in action.
そッ　それじゃあ…
ひざまずいて
T-Then-
Kneel down.
What?
えッ？
いいから
Just do it.
Hey, what are you staring at?
ちょっと　何じっと見てんのよ
ここにキスするんでしょ？
You're gonna kiss here, right?
あッ　ああ
Y-Yeah.
I'm gonna, but...
そうなんだけど…
あのさ　こっちも
相当恥ずかしいんだから
You know, this is pretty embarrassing for me too.
そこんとこ　よ～く考えてよね
Try to keep that in mind, okay?
分かってるよ
I... I know that.
なら　早くしなさいよ
Then... hurry up and do it.
うんッ　くすぐったい
It tickles.
女の子の肌って
こんなスベスベなのか
I never knew girls had such silky smooth skin.
唇が触れるだけで
こんなに気持ちがいいなんて…
Just touching it with my lips feels incredible.
Quit talking with your lips against me!
口つけたままで　しゃべらないでよ
うッ　うん
Are you done yet?
もう　いい？
〈そう言われてもな…
何だか　いい香りがするし〉
I don't know about that...
It smells really good for some reason.
〈ああ…
離すのがもったいないような〉
A-And it'd be a waste to just let go.
All right, if it's just for a little bit...
〈よし　ちょっと
ちょっとだけなら…〉
ひゃッ！　ちょっと
今なめたでしょ　うんッ！
H-Hey!  Did you just lick me?!
ダメ！
うわッ　何すんだよ！
No!
What are you doing?
We're done!
もう終わり！
上から服をかぶせたりして
Aren't you making it harder for me to
get away by putting your clothes over me?!
逃げられなくしてるのは　お前だろ
も～ッ
Nii-nii...
にぃに…
アハハハ…
想像以上のネタに走ったわね
That really was something!
How'd you like it?
どうだ
ええ　よ～く分かったわ
I know something well now.
あんたが悪い男だってね
悪くなんてないよ
You're a bad boy.
I'm not!
男らしいところを見せるなんて
言って　あんなことしたくせに？
Even after saying you'd show me
your manliness and doing all that?
That was...
それは…
Oh, yeah!
そう　隙があったから！
言うじゃない
Because you were wide open!
You sure know how to talk.
誰かの悪い影響が出てるんだよ
ウフフッ
Maybe someone's bad influence is working on me.
（薫・純一）ハハハ…
Well, whatever.
まあいいわ
相当恥ずかしかったけど
It was really embarrassing, but...
It was also fun in its own way.
それなりに面白くもあったし
男らしいかどうかは別として
Though whether it was manly or not is something else.
別なんだ…
当然でしょ
Something else, huh?
Of course it is.
あッ…
ねえ　バイトまで　まだ時間あるから
どこか行かない？
Hey, I have some time until my part-time job.
Wanna go somewhere?
えッ？　ああ
別にいいよ　どこ行く？
Uh, sure.
Where do you wanna go?
Let's see...
そうね…
じゃあ公園でも散歩してく？
How about a walk in the park?
うん　そうしようか
Sure, let's do that.
（薫・純一）うん？
う～ん　どうしよっか…
What should we do?
行くよ
えッ？
Let's go.
おい　こら　ボウズども
何？
Hey, boys.
What is it?
Want some help with that?
何とかしたげよっか？
えッ　ホントに？
でも…
Really?
But there's no way you can reach that high.
あんなの届かないよ
Hey, you should be able to reach it, right?
ねえ　あんたなら届くでしょ？
Don't be ridiculous.  That's way too high up.
ムチャ言うなよ
さすがに　あそこまでは
うんじゃ　あんたが下ね
はッ？
Well then, you'll be on the bottom.
ほら土台　さっさとしゃがむ
Come on, base.  Hurry up and get down.
I should've known that it'd come to this.
やっぱり　こうなるのか…
仕方ないでしょ
他に方法がないんだし
Well, of course.
There's no other way.
おにいちゃん大丈夫？
はい…
Onii-chan, you okay?
Yeah...
さて　よいしょっと…
Now then...
〈こッ　これは！
太ももの感触が何とも…〉
W-Whoa...
Her thighs feel really...
I'm ready.  Stand up.
いいわよ　立って
あッ　ああ
O-Okay.
よッ　よッ…
おっとっと…
おお～ッ！
いいじゃない　バッチリよ！
Nice, this is perfect.
でも　肩車なんかで届くのか？
Though, can you really reach it riding piggyback?
Of course not.
届かないわよ
えッ？　じゃあどうし…　おッ！
Well then, what are yo-?!
If you look up, I'll kill you.
上　見たら殺すわよ
はあ？　わッ！
おお～ッ
もう少し～ッ！
Just a little further!
よし！
・（男の子）やった～！
Got it!
Yes!
はい
おねえちゃん　すごい
Onee-chan, you're amazing!
カッコイイ
おい薫　危ないぞ　早く下りろよ
You're so cool!
Come on, Kaoru.  It's dangerous.
Hurry up and get down.
What's the matter?
何してんだよ　また肩貸すか？
Do you need my shoulders again?
It's not that.
違うの　あんたが見てるから
下りられないんだけど
I can't come down with you watching.
What?
えッ？
見えちゃうでしょ！
You'll see them, won't you?!
あッ　そういうことか…
チェッ　ケチ
Oh, I see.
Pfft.  Stingy.
What do you mean, "pfft"?
「チェッ」て何？　「ケチ」って何よ！
And what do you mean, "stingy"?!
Problem solved!
バッチリ解決！
イエーイ！
Yay!
お前ってホント　ムチャするよな
昔から困ってる人を
You really are reckless.
You've never been able to ignore someone in need.
ほっとけないっていうか
いけない　バイトに遅れちゃう！
Crap!  I'm gonna be late for work!
えッ？
ゴメン　私から誘っておいて
I'm sorry.
Even though I invited you, we weren't
able to take a walk in the park in the end.
結局　公園の散歩とか
できなかったね
いや　別にいいよ　また今度で
Oh, don't worry about it.
We'll do it another time.
ホント？
じゃあ　また今度ゆっくり
Really?
Okay.  Next time, we'll take our time!
バーイ！
バイバーイ！
Bye!
Bye-bye!
She seems... different from usual.
〈何か　いつもと違う〉
Was Kaoru... always that cute?
〈薫って　あんなに
かわいかったっけ？〉
〈あッ　何で僕
ドキドキしてるんだ？〉
Why is my heart pounding like this?
ねえねえ
うん？
Hey, hey.
結構いい女じゃん
もうチューとかしたの？
She's a pretty nice girl.
Have you kissed her yet?
えッ　ええ～ッ！
あッ
お母さん　お母さ…
Mom!
Mom-
Mom...
お母さん…
その人　誰？
Who... is he?
誰なのよ…
Who on Earth is he?
・～
Naze naze
なぜ　なぜ
Why, oh why?
My Heart kurushii no
マイハート　苦しいの
Why does my heart ache like this?
Daijoubu nante ne
「大丈夫」 なんてね
I tell you that everything's fine
Sokkenai furi shitari
素っ気ないフりしたり
And behave coldly
Namaiki mo urahara
ナマイキも　うらはら
I act outrageous and disagreeable
Saidaigen no tsuyogari
最大限の強がり
It's the ultimate bluff
Doushite kana namida dechau
どうしてかな  ナミダ出ちゃう
Why am I starting to cry?
Aitsu no kao matomo ni mirenai
あいつの顔  まともに見れない
あいつの顔　まともに見れない
I can't even look squarely at his face
Ashita wa kitto kinou yori
明日はきっと　昨日より
Tomorrow for sure, even more than yesterday
Tomodachi ijou no kankei ni naritai
友達以上の関係になりたい
I want us to become more than just friends
Ashita wa kitto yume mo kitto
明日はきっと  夢もきっと
明日はきっと　夢もきっと
Tomorrow for sure, and in my dreams for sure
Koi suru kimochi kirameku
恋する気持ち　キラメク
These feelings of love will shine brilliantly
Just A Friend
Such A Friend
Still A Friend
Naze naze
なぜ　なぜ
Why, oh why?
I Can't Tell You My Heart
Why can't I tell you what's in my heart?
Preview
Next episode preview.
Hey, Junichi.
Why were you at the library today?
Uh, I was...
Could it be...
I see, so you were also studying for the exams!
I'll need to work hard on Math, my weakest subject.
Y-Yeah... good luck!
I can't exactly tell her I was kissing Kaoru's belly button.
Next episode: "Betrayal".
Next Episode
Betrayal
Rihoko.  If you need any help in math, I'll teach you, okay?
Really?
Thank you!